// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "This refers to the particular strategy used by a writer to develop ideas.",
    answer: "Patterns of Development",
    options: [
      "Patterns of Creativity",
      "Patterns of Development",
      "Patterns of Empowerment",
      "Patterns of Symmetry"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What type of Pattern of Development that means to tell a story about people, places, events, dates, etc.?",
    answer: "Narration",
    options: [
      "Description",
      "Exemplification",
      "Definition",
      "Narration"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What type of Pattern of Development that gives information of what a person, an object, a place, or a situation is like?",
    answer: "Description",
    options: [
      "Description",
      "Exemplification",
      "Definition",
      "Narration"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What type of Pattern of Development that explains what a concept, term, or subject means, does, what something is used for, and what something looks like?",
    answer: "Definition",
    options: [
      "Description",
      "Exemplification",
      "Definition",
      "Narration"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What type of Pattern of Developement that uses specific or concrete examples to expound the main idea. uses signal phrases like for example, for instance, namely, consider the following, etc.?",
    answer: "Exemplification",
    options: [
      "Exemplification",
      "Classification",
      "Description",
      "Definition"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What type of Pattern of Developement sorts items, people, or objects to group together those with similar characteristics?",
    answer: "Classification",
    options: [
      "Exemplification",
      "Classification",
      "Description",
      "Definition"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What type of Pattern of Developement that means to identify the similarities of two different items?",
    answer: "Comparison",
    options: [
      "Cause and Effect",
      "Comparison",
      "Problem-solving",
      "Contrast"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What type of Pattern of Developement means to identify the differences between two similar items?",
    answer: "Contrast",
    options: [
      "Contrast",
      "Persuasion",
      "Problem-solving",
      "Comparison"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What type of Pattern of Developement means to identify the reasons and results of an occurrence?",
    answer: "Cause and Effect",
    options: [
      "Comparison",
      "Persuasion",
      "Problem-solving",
      "Cause and Effect"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What type of Pattern of Developement starts by identifying a problem and then proposes two or more solutions?",
    answer: "Problem-solving",
    options: [
      "Persuasion",
      "Problem-solving",
      "Cause and Effect",
      "Contrast"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What type of Pattern of Developement It intends to convince readers to believe in an idea or opinion and to do an action?",
    answer: "Persuasion",
    options: [
      "Comparison",
      "Persuasion",
      "Problem-solving",
      "Cause and Effect"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];